A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- JDR 3rd Fund photographs, 1968-1977; 1040
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Annual Report, Project Photos, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Stake, Robert - Evaluating the Arts in Education, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Asia Society / CEMREL - Jaipur Observatory - 1974 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Baldwin School of Puerto Rico - Photos with Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education - 1969/1970 Report - Portraits of Staff (Box 17, Folder 225)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education, 1969/70 Reports, Activities (Tearchers), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 226)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Bank Street College of Education, 1969/70 Report - School Scenes, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 227)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - ES'70 - Meeting, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 228)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - ES'70 - Portland, Oregon Program, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 229)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Mineola Public Schools - Arts Project Activities (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Arts in Education - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Caravan (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - PS 3-M - Final Report, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Oklahoma City Arts Council, Festival, 1973 April (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Ridge Street Schools, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Arts in education - K. Bloom - University City Schools - Project Photos, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 235)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University City Missouri - Meetings, Summer Workshop, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University City Missouri Schools - JDR 3rd visit, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Institute of American Indian Arts Theatre, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 238)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - National Chorale Council, 1970/71 Season, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 239)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - San Francisco Art Institute, Report, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 240)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - Columbia University Center for the Arts, Proposal, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University of Michigan Experimental Theatre Festival, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 242)
  - Arts in Education - K. Bloom - University of Southern California Joint Educational Project, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 243)